今天山姆·莱利踢足球
Today Sam Riley kicked a soccer ball...
狠狠砸中某小孩 他眼珠都爆出来了
and it hit another kid so hard his eye popped out.
帅呆了
Awesome!
是吗 眼珠真爆出来了吗
Really? His eye popped out.
-算了 -钻被窝咯 明天周六大日子哎
- Never mind. - Well, gotta hit the sack. Big Saturday tomorrow.
没错 某人过生日
That's right. It's somebody's birthday.
不止生日 iPad要开卖了
Not just that. The iPad comes out-
就在我生日这天
on my actual birthday.
像是乔帮主和上帝勾肩搭背地说
It's like Steve Jobs and God got together to say,
"我们爱你哟 菲尔"
"We love you, Phil."
那玩意儿到底棒在哪儿
What is so great about that doohickey anyhow?
"玩意儿" 艾丽·梅
"Doohickey," Elly May?
电影院 图书馆 音乐商店
It's a movie theater, a library and a music store...
都集成在那神奇的小本里
all rolled into one awesome pad.
图书馆知道吗 是个看书的地方
A library is a place where people get books.
电影院知道吗 是个约会的地方
A movie theater is a place where people go on dates.
我得把沙滩椅装到车里
I better load the beach chair into the trunk.
明早好坐着排队
I'm gonna need it for the line in the morning.
等等亲爱的
Wait, honey. Hang on.
你生日怎么能排一天队呢
You can't spend your birthday in line.
不会排一天啦
Well, not the whole day.
我6点去 不用你惦记
I have to be there at 6:00, you'll forget about it.
-10点就买到啦 -我去排怎么样
- Then I'm out by 10:00. - Why don't you let me do it?
克莱尔 没必要吧
Claire, you don't have to do that.
是没必要 但我想替你
No, I know, but I want to.
那样的话 你生日这天
And that way on your birthday
一睁眼 面前就是新玩具啦
you'll wake up and you'll have your brand-new toy.
好吧
Okay.
你将之称作"玩具"是大不敬
Well, in spite of you calling it a toy,
但明天貌似会超过我曾过得最开心的一个生日
this is shaping up to top the best birthday I ever had.
感谢上帝 再不用听那故事
Oh, thank God we don't have to hear that stupid story
-什么地方来着 -在欢乐地带球场
- about that place... - It was called the Fun Zone.
那年我11岁
I was 11.
连续击中10个直线快球
I hit 10 straight fastballs in the batting cage.
然后我的铁哥们杰夫·斯威尼冒出来
Then my best friend Jeff Sweeney stepped in
被我正中胯下
and took one in the groin.
我喊道 又中两"球"
I yelled out "Ball two!"
所有人爆笑
Everybody laughed.
那时我就知道 我很搞笑
That was when I knew I was funny.
晚安
Good night.
B-E-L-I-E-V-E 相信
B-E-L-I-E-V-E. Believe.
中间不是E-I吗 你确定吗
Are you sure there's not an "E-I" In the middle?
- 不 是I-E -好样滴 宝贝
- No. It's "I-E." - Good, papi!
我绕不晕你 你老师也别想成功
If I can't fool you, then your teachers can't fool you either.
老师没必要绕晕我吧
I don't think they're trying to fool me.
猜猜我给菲尔买了什么生日礼物
Wait until you see what I got Phil for his birthday.
天维购物淘到的
I found it on the SkyMall catalog.
啧啧 不是那种会说话的闹钟吧
Ay. It's not one of those talking alarm clocks?
"6:05啦 6:25啦 醒醒啦醒醒啦"
"It's 6:05. It's 6:25. Wake up. Wake up."
比那个棒多了 一套紫檀木棋
Even better. A rosewood chess set.
话说 不如我等会再包装
As matter of fact, before I wrap this thing,
我们先来一局怎么样
what say we take it for a spin?
来吧曼尼 我教你
Come on, Manny. I'll teach you.
他会下的啦 他老爸教过的
He knows how to play. His father taught him.
我要教他正经下法 不是哥伦比亚版的
I'm gonna teach him real chess, not the Colombian version.
在我们这 棋子是用来下的
We actually use the pieces to play the game,
不是用来藏毒走私的
not smuggle stuff out of the country.
那你也少来玩我这哥伦比亚女子
I know one Colombian piece you won't be playing with later.
曼尼快来 试试你能耐
Manny, come on. Let's see what you got.
会让你大吃一惊的
You'll be surprised.
曼尼棋艺高超 杰的棋品可不咋滴
Manny's an excellent player, but Jay is a grumpy loser.
输了就生闷气 吊脸子 还摔门
He mopes, he makes the face, he slams the door,
摔完门还不承认
then he said he didn't slam the door.
让他赢比较好啦
It's better that he wins.
我来
Um, I got this.
没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
好啦 别哭啦
It's okay. It's okay.
-小卡 -别吵我
- Cam! - Leave me alone.
莉莉 莉莉房里有个人
There's a...there's a man in Lily's room.
莉莉房里有个人啊
There's a man in Lily's room!
大棒走起
It's go time.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
是我是我 别打 是我
It's me, it's me, it's me, it's me.
她没事
She's fine.
邻居的监控器和我们串线了
We must have just heard a neighbor with the same monitor.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
老天 要是有蜘蛛闯入
Boy, if a spider would have broken in here,
你捏个报纸也就能吓吓它而已
he would have been in trouble.
灯光烧烤夹
Light-up barbecue tongs.
我就给菲尔准备了这破礼物
This was the lame gift I got Phil.
所以5点起床排队 我郁闷吗
So, was I bummed to get up at 5:00 and wait in line?
不 不会 我总算能给老公
No. No, because I was finally getting my husband
买到梦寐以求的礼物了
something that he really, really wanted.
我和他一样兴奋
I was every bit as excited as he was.
不行
No.
嘿 哥们
Hey, buddy.
昨天输给我 没生气吧
I hope you're not upset about our chess match yesterday.
再来一盘怎么样
Hey, what do you say we play again?
-我挺好 -态度不错
- I'm good. - That's the spirit.
我给你下载的
Downloaded this for you.
儿童级国际象棋入门
It's kind of a kid's guide to chess.
不了 杰 我好得很
No, Jay. I'm good.
下棋不无聊的 可以很有趣嘛
Nah, it's not all dry like that. They have fun with it.
看 可以用蜡笔给小人上色呢
See, you can color in the little players with your crayons.
还真让我兴趣大增
Now you are making me want to play again.
有兴趣就对了 我们来打个赌吧
Now we're lighting a fire. Let me toss this out.
如果终有一天 你下赢了我
If you beat me, if that day should ever come,
我就给你...
I'll give you-
-你那块表 -哟 早看上了啊
- I want your watch. - Wow, you had that loaded up.
成 来吧
Okay. Game on.
来 你先下
Now, I want you to go first.
记住 努力清出中路
Now remember, try to open up the middle of the board.
我觉得你该走两步
I'd have moved that guy two spaces.
更有攻击性
More aggressive.
皇后也别那么早出来
And you don't want to bring your queen out that quickly.
看 它应该守在原地的
See, now you could've protected that with that,
它一动 就露了...
but now you're vulnerable-
-将军 -哈? 什么
- Checkmate. - Huh? What?
怎么将的
How'd you do that?
你肯定猜不到
You will not believe what's going on
杰克和黛比家出了什么事
at Jake and Debbie's house.
-谁 -和我们串线那家 肯定就住附近
-Who? -The people on the monitor. They must live nearby.
他家太狗血了
So much drama.
杰克跟黛比说 他要加班
Okay, Jake told Debbie that he had to work late.
黛比打给他老板
So she called his boss
发现没加班 抓包
and found out that he didn't. Busted!
她就打了一早上电话
So she spent all morning on the phone
跟她妈妈哭啊哭啊哭
crying and crying and crying to her mother...
说如果杰克再"加班"
and said if Jake has to work "late" one more time,
她就要离婚
she's filing for divorce.
就这样吗 我端上狗血大菜
That's it? I give you that tasty dish
你就只"哈"一声吗
and all you give me is a "Huh"?
对不起小卡 昨晚我吓呆了
I-I'm s- Cam, I froze last night.
真是呆了
I froze.
我以为莉莉有危险 就吓呆了
I thought Lily was in danger and I froze.
可你没有 你立刻行动
But not you. No, you sprung right into action.
居然还拉风地说了句"走起"
You even had the cool "It's go time" line.
那是本能啦 我做过一年交管员
That comes to me naturally. I spent a year as a crossing guard.
小卡 我算是什么爸爸啊
Cam, I mean, what kind of parent am I
连自己的家人都保护不了
if I can't even protect my own family, you know?
我真想有那么一次无所畏惧
Just once I would love to be the guy with no fear...
站起来 该 该出手时就出手
who can stand up and, I don't know, you know, kick some ass.
你那小粉拳挥得真萌
You're so cute when you're angry with your little fists.
真想把你装进口袋里
Just wanna put you in my pocket.
老爸下楼了
Think he's coming.
-来了吗 -来了来了
- He's coming? - Here he comes.
-老爸 -生日快乐
- Dad! - Happy birthday!
孩子们 帅呆了
You guys! That's awesome.
-谁送来的气球 -小卡和米奇尔
- Oh, who are these from? - Cam and Mitchell.
典型的基情温馨
Those guys are a class act.
我们给你做早餐呢
We're making you breakfast.
法式华夫饼哦
French waffle cakes.
我猜猜 两片法式吐司夹华夫
Let me guess: One waffle in between two pieces of French toast
外面裹着煎饼
wrapped in a pancake.
全对
Nailed it.
过来吧孩儿们
Bring it in here, monkeys.
老爸爱你们 快过来
Love you! Get over here!
真棒
Good enough.
老妈人呢
Where's Mom?
你是说史上最棒的女人吗
You mean the greatest woman in the world?
正在苹果店门外排队呢
She is standing in line at the Apple Store,
要实现我所有的生日愿望
making all my birthday wishes come true.
看看味道怎样
Let's see how these bad boys taste.
-别碰 -老天 烫
- Oh, no... - Son of a... Oh! It's hot!
-没事吧 -刚出炉是吧 真是
- Are you okay? - Fresh out of the oven? That is...
-要冰块吗 -要
- Do you want some ice? - Yes.
靠 真是...
Oh, man! This...
-舒服多了 舒服舒服 -对不起 老爸
- Oh, that feels better. That feels better. - Sorry, Dad.
没有 太诡异了
No, it actually- That feels weird.
换了种疼法
That burns in a different way!
烤盘别洗啊 我皮还黏在上面呢
Don't wash this until we see if I can get my skin back. Okay?
让我看看
Let me see it!
不行 派对要晚上才开始呢
No! Your party's not until tonight.
你得等等
You're just gonna have to wait.
让我看看包装袋嘛 留在车里了吗
Just let me see the bag. Did you leave it in the car?
-对啊 -谁招待你的
- Yeah! - Hey, who'd you deal with?
是叫莫哈吗 他们管他叫"兽男"
Was it a guy named Mehar? They call him "The beast."
矮个子 他肯定忙着疯狂搬货
He's a tiny guy. He must've move a ton of product.
吊胃口哈 我喜欢
I kinda love that you're making me wait.
你是史上最棒老婆啦
You are the best wife ever!
史上最棒 绝对的
我没买到iPad
I didn't get you the iPad.
我到的时候已经卖光了
I got to the store and they were all out.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
我不懂 我网友都买到了
I don't understand. My online buddies got it.
高考落榜君和机器兄8点才到店里
SAT800 and Brobot didn't get there until 8:00.
你肯定比他们早
And you definitely got there before they did,
你不是六点半就去了
because you got there at 6:30.
不不不 你没早去吗 你上哪去了
No, no, no! You didn't get there at 6:30? Where were you?
我闹钟定了五点的
I set the alarm for 5:00.
起床下楼 结果又睡着了
I got up, I came downstairs, I fell asleep.
不要啊 老天爷
No! Oh, my goodness.
我做了什么 我做了什么
What have I done? What have I done?
-我该自己去的 -亲爱的 没事
- I should've done this myself. - Sweetie, you know what?
下周会补货的呀
They're gonna get more in next week.
下周
Next week?
让抢鲜族等下周 你太残忍了
That's the worst thing you can say to an early adopter.
你上哪去
Where are you going?
去找个重视别人生日的地方
To a place where birthdays still mean something.
我去开门
I'll get that.
-曼尼 -米奇尔
- Hi, Manny. - Mitchell?
你有何贵干呀
What are you doing here at...
现在时间 周六下午4点17分
4:17 on a Saturday afternoon?
我来还老爸的工具包
Oh, I'm just returning my dad's belt of tools, so-
周六下午4点17分吗
At 4:17 on a Saturday afternoon?
你没别的事可干了吗
Don't you have something better to do?
-装扮成功吗 -什么
- So, were you a big hit? - What do you mean?
你借这玩意多半是参加化妆派对嘛
Well, I just assumed there was some kind of costume party.
小卡扮印度阿三是不
Was Cam the Indian?
不 跟你说 爸
No. For your information, Dad,
我们确实是在家建了东西
we were actually doing a little construction at the house.
建了什么
What'd you build?
礼品包装小站
A gift-wrapping station.
真够基情的哈
And we're back.
-谢了 -不客气
- So, thank you for that. - You're welcome.
老爸 你记不记得我11岁时
Hey, uh, Dad, do you remember when I was, probably 11...
你教我拳击 我半途而废来着
and you were teaching me how to fight, and then I quit?
是啊 你说你要学的招数
Yeah, when you said everything you needed to learn
《西区故事》那种歌舞片里都有
you'd learn from West Side Story.
-对 -花拳绣腿好用吗
- Yeah. - How'd that work out for you?
哪天斗了舞 一定告诉你
If I'm ever in a dance fight, I'll let you know.
那 你还想教我吗
So, yeah- Is the offer, uh, still good?
怎么了 你和小卡闹矛盾啦
Why? What's the matter? You got problems with Cam?
怎么会呢 你咋猜那个
No! Why would you say that?
拜托 和男人同居哎
Well, come on. I mean, you know, sharing a room with a guy?
我跟我弟弟睡过上下铺 天天暴力
I bunked with my brother. I know that can get pretty rough.
我和小卡可不睡上下铺
I don't "bunk" with Cam.
爸 我就是想学点自卫术
Dad, I just wanna learn a little self-defense, you know.
还记得哪招 耍来看看
Show me what you remember.
-现 现在吗 -来吧
- Right now? - Yeah.
好吧 老天 拇指外扣
Okay, uh- Gosh, uh- Thumbs out.
-没错 乖仔 -然后
- Thumbs. Attaboy. - And then-
不咋漂亮 是不
That wasn't- That wasn't very pretty, was it?
其实 恐怕是太"漂亮"了
You know what? Maybe it was a little too pretty.
没错
That's the thing.
起飞了哈
Here it goes.
老天
Oh! Oh, man!
哥们
Buddy!
你起跳点太低了 才没飞起来
Think the problem is, you're not jumping from high enough.
去车库顶试试
You should get on top of the garage.
艾丽克斯 别害你小弟了
Alex, stop trying to kill your brother.
各位 妈妈要求助你们
Listen, guys, I need your help.
得给老爸找个iPad来
We've gotta find your dad one of those iPad thingies.
海莉 给你朋友群发短信
So, Haley, text everyone you know.
艾丽克斯 Facebook 推特什么的都发一圈
Alex? Facebook, chat, tweet, buzz, bling,
我不懂那些玩意 你要通过一切渠道
I don't know! Just do what you have to do.
千万找个iPad来 好吗
We have got to find one of these iPads. Okay?
卢克小可爱 别挡路
Luke? Sweetie, that means stay out of everyone's way
也别吸氢气
and stop inhaling the balloons.
我哪有吸氢气
I'm not inhaling them.
少撒谎了
Stop lying.
她怎么发现的
How did she know?
妈妈有没教你 别坐陌生人的车
Didn't your mama teach you never to take a ride from a stranger?
快放假了吧
Got a little vacation time coming up?
上月球好好玩吧
Have fun on the moon!
最近身体不爽是吗
Not feeling too well lately?
来看看医生
Maybe you should come see the doctor...
哥帮你解决
and I'll get rid of it!
你瞎嚷嚷啥呢
What's that supposed to mean?
请注意 参加菲尔生日派对的朋友们
Attention. If you're here for Phil's birthday party,
请到野餐区集合
they're gathering in the picnic area.
菲尔的生日派对
Phil's birthday party.
我老婆知道我会来这
My wife knew I'd be here.
给我准备了派对哎
She put together a whole party for me.
这能弥补iPad的事儿吗
Does that really make up for not getting an iPad?
我跟你交心了 你可别挑拨我们
Don't make me sorry I shared that with you. Okay?
拜啦各位
See you, fellas.
侬好呀
Howdy-do!
广播说菲尔的生日派对在这
I just heard the announcement for Phil's birthday party.
对的 拐弯就是
Oh, yeah. It's right around the corner.
-太棒了 -好好玩
- Awesome. - Have fun!
谢谢你 美女
Thank you. Thanks, my lady.
冰激凌蛋糕吗 真棒
Ice-cream cake? Ice-cream cake's good.
菲尔 生日快乐
Happy birthday, Phil!
太帅了
This is awesome!
-生日快乐 -生日快乐
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!
生日快乐 宝贝
Happy birthday, sweetie.
-生日快乐 -玩得开心呀
- Happy birthday. - Have a really good birthday.
-看到蛋糕了吗 -超棒的
- Did you see the cake? - Oh, yeah. It's great.
喂
Hello?
没事 我哄小孩睡觉呢
No, that's fine, I'm just putting the baby down.
那是杰克 出轨的那个
Okay, that's Jake. He's the one that's having an affair.
-我知道的 -明晚没问题
- I know. - Yeah, I can do it tomorrow night.
向我老婆编个谎就行
I'll just give my wife some excuse.
混蛋汉子
Men are pigs.
-那也没办法 -有呀
- I don't really have a choice, do I? - Yeah.
别劈腿不行吗
You could not cheat on her! How about that?
我得给她个惊喜嘛
Because it has to be a surprise.
等我跟她外婆说起意大利语
When she hears me speaking Italian to her grandmother,
我偷偷摸摸这么长时间也值了
it'll be worth all this sneaking around.
莉莉 我猜错了 他是个好男人啊
Lily, I had it backwards. He's wonderful.
别担心 我就说要加班
Don't worry. I'll just tell her I'm working late.
不行杰克 别那么说
No, Jake, don't do that.
说加班你就惨了
That's the worst thing you could do.
晚安啦[意大利语]
Buonanotte.
坏了莉莉 我们要怎么办
Oh, no, Lily, what are we gonna do?
得帮帮他们啊
We have to fix this.
米奇尔 我就教你几招
Okay, Mitchell, I'm gonna teach you
基本的巴西柔术吧
a couple of basic Brazilian jiu-jitsu moves.
现在 来打我
Now, just attack me.
什么
I'm sorry- What?
释放你内心的怨恨
Take any deep-seated anger you may have,
冲过来打我吧
get a running start and come at me.
老爸 我没记恨过你啊
Dad, I don't have any deep-seated anger.
记得那次万圣节
Remember that Halloween when
我不让你扮奥利维亚·纽顿-约翰吗
I wouldn't let you go as Olivia Newton-John?
懂了吧 借力打力
You see what I did? I used your momentum against you.
格雷西柔术创始人教我的
I learned this choke from the Gracie brothers.
这招叫"伏狮锁"
It's called the lion killer- mata lella.
-懂 -试试挣脱 挣一下
- Okay. - Now try to get out. Try to get out.
-难不 -挣不开
- See? - I can't.
挣不开就对了
Yeah, all right. Now-
-我要晕了 -这招就厉害在
- Passing out... - See, the beauty of this is,
你不用贸然攻击
you don't have to make the first move.
对手可能会轻敌嘛
You know, chances are your opponent's gonna be overconfident.
以为你是个菜鸟
He's gonna think you don't know anything.
反而被骗 就显得很二
Basically, he's being suckered into thinking-
曼尼 曼尼这小子耍我
Manny. Manny, that little bastard, he hustled me.
糟
Oh, crap.
糟了 米奇尔
Ah, crap. Mitchell!
得 吸气 加油
Oh, crap. All right. Come on. Breathe.
好小子 快醒来
Attaboy. You all right? Coming around.
-我怎么趴地上了 -醒过来 米奇尔
- Why am I on the floor?- Come on, Mitchell.
海莉 我又没买着
Haley, I just struck out again.
拜托给点好消息
Please tell me you have some good news.
格氏又进了一批货
Okay, so The Grove just got a new shipment.
我短信你地址
I'm texting you the directions now.
很好 很好 真棒真棒
Oh! Okay, that's good. That's good. That's good.
我这就去 立刻滚去
I'm there. I'm on that.
那小子把我手表骗走了
That kid stole my watch.
-啥 -什么
- Huh? - What?
他骗我跟他下棋
He hustled me at chess.
你不是保证让他赢吗
I thought you promised you were gonna let him win.
-我让他赢了一盘 -等等 你也知道
- I did the first time. - Wait a minute. You're in on it too?
曼尼 换派对衣服去
Manny, go and get dressed for the party.
能洗个澡吗
Do I have time for a steam?
-行 但要快 -好
- Yeah, but a quick one. - Okay.
干嘛叫他输给我
Why tell him to lose to me?
你一输棋就发小孩脾气
Because you're like a baby when you don't win.
乱踢东西 皱眉头
With the kicking and the eyebrows...
还狂吃瓜子
and the angry eating of the sunflower seeds.
不是那样的
Actually, that's not true.
输给小天才 我怎么会不服气呢
I don't mind losing to a chess genius, which Manny obviously is.
他天才 他还没我下得好呢
Chess genius? He's not even as good as I am.
你下棋不怎么样啊
You're not that good in chess.
-蜜月那次输给我了啊 -我让你的
- I beat you on our honeymoon. - Or did I let you win?
你才没让我
You didn't let me win.
我干嘛要把皇后送入你的魔爪 杰
Why would I sacrifice my queen for your pawn, Jay?
别哼了
Stop saying that.
卢克 宝贝 怎么了
Luke, honey, hi. What's going on?
老爸的蛋糕送来了
They guy came with Dad's cake,
可它缺了一块
but just so you know, it's missing a piece.
-你偷吃老爸蛋糕了吗 -没啊
- Luke, did you take a bite out of your father's cake? - No.
-别撒谎 卢克 -我哪有
- Stop lying, Luke. - I'm not lying.
哦对 我用你的卡付了钱
By the way, I used your credit card to pay him.
没问题吧
Is that all right?
没问题啊
Oh, no, that's fine.
我把钱包留给你们就是为这个的嘛
Whatever. That's why I left the wallet there.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
我把钱包留家里了
I left the wallet there! I left the wa-
你可怜的老爸
Your poor father.
我们乱成一团
All this running around,
他肯定以为没人在乎他生日
and he's gonna think nobody cares about him on his birthday.
再来点蛋糕吗
More cake?
行啊 小菲尔
Why not, Little Phil?
反正我也没地儿去
I got no place else to go.
先生 先生 打扰你了
Sir! Sir! Sir, hi. Excuse me.
我有点唐突
Um, yes. I know this is highly unusual,
但我需要你帮忙 挽救一段婚姻
but I need your help to save a marriage.
这附近有对夫妇
There is a couple in this neighborhood...
就因为一个小误会 快要离婚了
that is about to get a divorce for a simple misunderstanding.
他们叫杰克和黛比
Their name is Jake and Debbie.
我知道您宣过誓
And I know you've taken an oath...
不能泄露他人住址
to not tell people where other people live,
我也尊重您
and I respect that,
但我们能不能想办法
but maybe we could work out some sort of
设计一套暗号
super secretive spy signal,
比如你挠左耳
where if you scratch your left ear,
暗示我他们住在左手边
you know, maybe they live on the left,
如果挠右耳 就是...
and if you scratch your right ear, they live on-
就住这
They live right here.
我不会说出去的
This conversation never happened.
-抱歉晚了 -感谢上帝
- Sorry. - Oh, thank God!
谢谢你 谢谢
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
老爸把我整晕了
Dad just put me to sleep.
他给你讲催眠的打猎故事了吧
The hunting story.
不是啦
Hmm. No.
老天 你可不能插队 对不起
Oh, my gosh, no. You can't cut the line. Sorry.
-我本来就排这 -哪有
- I was here. - Uh-uh.
我排了一个半小时
I-I've been here for an hour and a half
都没看见你 你这是插队
and you haven't been, so you cut the line.
-你管我 -这位先生
- Whatever. - Whoa. Excuse me, sir.
您好像没弄清楚
I don't think you understand.
你不可以插队的
You're not getting in front of us.
淡定点啦 红毛小子
Calm down, gingerbread.
-你走还是不走 -不走
- Are you gonna move or not? - No.
别啊
Oh, no.
那我别无选择
Then you leave me no choice.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
晕吧你
Go to sleep.
快点 快晕过去
Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
没晕啊
No.
-米奇尔你干什么 放开他 -闭嘴
- Mitchell, what are you doing? Get off of him. - Shut up.
-他就要晕了 -才没有呢
- He's about to go to sleep. - No, I'm not.
请不要打架 三位请出列
Okay, folks. Break this up. You three- out of line.
抱歉先生 我和他们无关
Oh, no. I'm sorry, sir. I didn't have anything to do with this.
我只是排队买iPad而已
I'm just waiting in line to get an iPad.
我都不认识他
I don't even know this guy.
老天 我得用你的信用卡
Oh, my God. I need your credit card.
-是他挑事 -闭嘴 你怎么还不晕
- He's the problem. - Shut up! You're supposed to be asleep.
-没事我拿到了 -放开我
- It's okay. I have it. - Get off!
-我拿到了 -什么
- I've got it. - What?
你的卡 我没犯事 没犯事
I've got your card. I'm good. No, I'm good.
我排在这呢 这儿
I'm good. I'm here. I'm here!
我要给我老公买iPad啊
I've gotta get my husband an iPad!
生日快乐的秘诀就是 别期待太多
Key to a good birthday? Low expectations.
我以为能有iPad 期待错了
Thought I was getting an iPad. I was wrong about that.
以为球场有惊喜派对
Thought I was getting a surprise party at the batting cages.
不好意思 大菲尔
Sorry, Big Phil.
我觉得 说到底
Guess when it comes right down to it,
我就跟被踢中蛋蛋的杰夫·斯威尼一样
we're all just Jeff Sweeney taking a fastball to the plums.
老爸 蛋糕掉地下了
Hey, um, Dad, your cake fell off the counter,
但小卡舅夫正补救呢
but Uncle Cam's trying to fix it.
他只会偷吃掉
He won't.
披萨一直都没送来
And the pizzas never showed up.
没来就没来呗
And they won't!
基情小气球啊
Hey, balloons.
得 反正没法知道了
Fine. I guess we'll never know.
要么现在见分晓
Or we can find out right now.
曼尼 棋盘给我
Yeah, Manny, give me the chess set.
-送我棋盘啊 -待会再给你
- Oh, it's a chess set. - Yeah. You'll get it later.
我们得决一死战
We got something to settle now.
-往里走 - 生日快乐 菲尔
- Go in there. - Happy birthday, Phil.
一定快乐哟
Happy happy.
好香 克莱尔烤了干酪吗
Is that Claire's baked brie I smell?
没
No.
小卡小卡 你不会相信的
Oh, Cam, Cam, you'll never believe what happened.
-生日快乐 菲尔 -当然啦
- Happy birthday, Phil! - Sure!
你绝不会相信的
You'll never believe what happened.
我和人打架了
I got in trouble for fighting.
我们还挽救了一段婚姻
And we saved a marriage.
-今天真是史上最棒 -没错
- Well, this is the best day ever. - It really is.
可不是嘛
Ain't it though?
宝贝 看我这招
Look at this, papi, huh?
淡定
Easy.
别唱《冠军之歌》[皇后乐队名曲]
You can't sing "We Are the Champions"...
你的皇后都没了
without your queen.
该死 要是我输了 我就烧掉这房子
Damn it! Listen, I lose and I burn this house down!
-看这儿 -亲爱的 亲爱的
- Ah, but look at this... - Honey, honey.
我们闹什么呢 太滑稽了
What are we doing? This is ridiculous.
我们总有个要赢
One of us is gonna win the game,
另一个就不爽 只会两败俱伤
the other's gonna feel lousy, and we both lose.
成啊 把我的礼物扔地上吧
Yeah, just leave my birthday present on the floor.
好老婆 她已经赢定了
That's my girl. She had me.
我没戏了 我知道的
There was no way I could win. I knew it.
幸好她不知道
I'm just glad she didn't know it yet.
只需两步 就能杀他个...
Two moves, and then-
我可是个下棋高手
I'm a very good chess player.
但我更是个好老婆
But I'm a better wife.
-买到了吗 -没有
- Hey, did you get it? - No.
-爸爸怎么样 -古怪 更古怪了
- How's your dad? - Acting weird... er.
-老婆 -亲爱的
- Hey, wife. - Honey, hi.
-是这样 -妈妈
- Um, listen... - Mom.
卢克 等会再说
Yeah, Luke, hang on one second.
老婆 没关系啦 我已经没感觉了
Honey, it's okay. I don't feel things anymore.
-可我想让你... -妈妈
- But, sweetie, I want you to feel... - Mom!
卢克我一会就来 你上哪去
Luke, I'll be with you in just a second. Where are you going?
去院子里拿铲子 清理我的蛋糕
Just heading out to the yard to get a shovel for my cake.
-老妈 -卢克你要干嘛
- Mom. - Luke, what do you want?
我上了老爸的电脑
I went on Dad's computer,
联系了他的宅男网友们
contacted some of his geek friends,
说老爸快死了
told them that he was dying
有个iPad才能瞑目
and his last wish was an iPad.
卢克 我怎么教你的
Luke, what have I told you about-
有个人很同情 就送来台多余的
One of them felt so bad, they brought over an extra.
上帝啊 你拿到了 你这个乖仔撒谎精
Oh, my God. You got it. You beautiful little liar!
老爸回来了
Here comes Dad.
谁想吃蛋糕呀
Who wants some cake?
我之前想 可我不想吃...
I used to, but I don't desire food any-
老天 你买到了
Oh, my God. You got it!
我说了半天不在乎
All this time I said I didn't care,
可我真想要 超想要的
but I do care. I care so much!
-想吹蜡烛吗 -好
- Do you want to blow out the candles? - Yes.
吹吧 使劲
Go on. Go.
居然真能吹灭
It did not just do that!
-是真的 -老婆我爱你
- Yes, it did! - Honey!
瞧这刚出炉热乎乎的iPad啊
Oh, who's ready for the first day of the rest of their lives?
-菲尔 生日快乐 -看啊
- Phil, happy birthday! - Look at this!
-我能摸摸吗 -摸 别掐 摸摸
- Can I touch it? - Yeah, not so hard, but touch it.
摸它 别摸 摸 别摸
Touch it, but don't touch it. Touch it, but don't touch it.
对不起 我不该怀疑你
I'm so sorry I ever doubted you.
我爱你
I love you.
感谢上帝送来了那个人
Thank God that guy came over.
他叫什么来着
What did he say his name was?
他没说 肯定是位天使
He didn't. Must be an angel.
听到了吗 说我是天使呢
Did you hear that? I'm an angel.
-或者是个变态 -对啊
- Or some creepy perv. - Yeah.
他怎么知道的 恶心
How did he know? Eww.
-我该报警吗 -没错 报警吧
- Maybe I should call the police. - You should call the police.
-这就报 -他们从此幸福地生活在一起
- I'm gonna call the police. - And they lived happily ever after.
别啊小卡 你上哪去 才刚开始精彩
No, Cam. Where are you going? It was just getting good.
我想听 多好的节目
I want- That's my program.
我爱你
I love you.
-我也爱你 亲爱的 -好吧
- I love you too, honey. - Oh. Okay.